Contacts

- 6967221@gmail.com
- Fantazer21
- in ilya-stepanov-044790200
- Fantazer21
- Fantazer21

Skills

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap
- Figma
- ES2016+
- Java Script
- React
- React-native
- Material-UI
- Unit-tests
- Axios
- Redux
- Redux-thunk
- Redux-saga
- TypeScript
- Git
- Node.JS
- English B2
- Serbo-Croatian A1

Education

- 2007-2012, Ivanovo State Power University
- 2021, IT-incubator

Ilya Stepanov

FRONT-END DEVELOPER-

About me

Front-end developer with commercial experience in software development. Have experience in developing and building applications using practices such as REST architecture, containerization, and high availability patterns, design patterns and front-end design systems, SOLID, and unit testing. Implemented a couple of projects using different front-end technologies such as TypeScript, React, React-Native, Redux. Always keeping an eye on making things better and improving performance, code quality, and customer satisfaction. Excellent communication and collaborative skills

Experience

TRAVEL ASK - MOSCOW, 2022 - till now

React-Native developer

React Native, Redux, Redux Saga, React Navigation, Figma, MobX, GIT, Custom time-metric system

- Built a React native app for travelers.
- Creating new components such as functional and class.
- Supporting and fixing bugs.
- Add a custom metric and features with authorization.
- Rewriting old code on Typescript.

AKVELON - IVANOVO, 2021 - 2022

Frontend developer

React, TypeScript, Redux, Redux-Thunk, Material UI, Ant Design, Figma, Jest, Trello, Microsoft Boards, GIT

- Web applications(frontend part) developing
- Refactoring, re-design, code reviews, performance and async code
- Fixing bugs.
- Creating a desktop version of the web shop from scratch.

GARPIX - IVANOVO, 2021 - 2021

Junior Frontend developer

JS, SASS, HTML, GIT

- Creating interactive SPA using JS, SASS, HTML.
- Fixing bugs.
- Adding special features to the current project.

FREELANCE - PODGORICA, 2020 - till now

Freelance as a Frontend developer

React, REDUX, JS, SASS, HTML, Figma

- Reusable components development.
- Unit Testing and StoryBook components.
- Creating SPA